Thank you for your hard work. It has been fun.
Boat Race Breeze, which is expanding its activities, has another good story to tell here.
We have been getting a lot of requests to build car cars for some time now to help us expand our activities.
We have been getting a lot of meh!
Now we are selling the goods to go buy one!
Wait, are you serious? You did it, folks. It's going on sale.
That's great!
We're still in the process of deciding on the design and stuff.
Not this one?
Not this one. This is a little brush.
You're the director, so you're the one who should take the director's risk.
I'm so glad!
We'll discuss the design with you today.
You're a producer!
I thought so.
Thank you very much. Wait, that's great!
First of all, I'd like to add a color.
First of all, this one.
Eh, pretty! Navy.
White.
Eh, cute! But white is nice, too. It looks nice.
Oh, I see.
Last, black.
Black. The one I'm wearing now.
But isn't this the image? A collaborative boat race.
Maybe one of the sleeves would be better.
This is probably what everyone is looking for.
Then I guess it's black.
Let's go with black. It's easy for everyone to wear.
Cattie in black settlement!
It's the kind of thing I made at random this summer, thinking it would be made into this kind of merchandise.
It's amazing! Just for making this.
I even designed the logo properly.
Oh, wow!
You got a designer?
You must be very important. He's been very good to me.
It's amazing. It looks like a boat.
It looks like a wave.
Is it still there?
Is there more?
Oh, wait, that's great!
This is also a wave design.
Oh, and this one?
This one is the closest to the current one.
But it's a little blurry.
Oh, it's cute!
It looks like a wave.
It's true! Isn't this one good?
It's like, "This is a super good version.
We're so used to seeing this,
F1 once now.
I like it in my opinion.
I'm looking forward to seeing the director first.
Yes, oh, I see!
Can I decide everything?
Why not us, too?
Hey, wait!
But this one is cute.
Isn't this the one?
Isn't this one?
That's it.
That's the one!
This is good.
Let's go with that one.
Yes, let's do that one.
Then what the heck...
This one's boring.
Here.
Random.
I'm gonna put in a kybul.
I mean, it's really fucked up, but really...
What do you mean?
I can't pick any of the numbers 1 through 1.
I can't pick one, but if you buy it and look at my right arm.
I mean, if you buy it and look at your right arm, you'll see three letters engraved on it.
A trifecta.
That's so funny.
Like 612.
I'm going to have to buy all of them from now on.
I'm going to have to buy it every time.
I'll have to buy it every time.
That's great.
It's random, and it's awesome.
And the stickers, too.
Oh, my gosh, they're absolutely adorable!
People are putting them on the backs of their phones and stuff.
I'll see you next time.
Yes, what is it?
A visual shoot.
Wait, you're filming for this merchandise?
Me?
Merchandise, and the official site, and the sales site.
Wait, you can do the official site?
Yes, it's ready.
Thank you very much. You've come a long way, Ecolab Boat Racing Club. I'm surprised, to be honest.
Let's do our best. I hope you're really looking forward to it. We're already working hard on the visuals, and the staff is going to create a website for us.
We are planning to create a website that we are very particular about. It's a website for the Ecolab Boat Racing Club's food only, right?
As a food-only part of the site, what are the future plans for the site? How about sales?
Then maybe we can finally go to Omura. I've already had a lot of people tell me that they definitely want to go.
I think it will be even more fun if you come to the boat race track wearing this. Please look forward to it. I will do my best. Please wait for me.
Is it done?
Did you do it?
Like this.
Oh, my God!
It's all on YouTube.
Wait, that's great.
From the quotes.
All of it.
This is the site?
It's a website.
Try drawing on it.
Oh, my God.
I'm going to take some more and some more.
Pose
Ice faculty
Nice, nice
Ice cream
Cute
Oh, nice, that looks about right.
Rust
Yes, yes
Great!
That's a big help!
Why does this cut off my face?
Rust!
How's it going back there?
It's not good.
It's kind of like a slight tilt.
A little body shake.
Nice! Cute!
Last number three.
More?
There's still something more.
Yes! That's all!
Thank you very much!
Yes! So, that's it.
I just finished taking pictures of the goods!
Yay!
Yes! This is the
Icologe Mortress Club
The official hoodie!
will go on sale tomorrow!
and the website is open today.
The website seems to be open, too.
This is the official hoodie of the Icologo Mortress Club
The official hoodies are
It is available in two sizes
Lady's size M and
and XL for the mais size.
6800 yen!
I'm wearing the XL right now!
I hope everyone is looking forward to these numbers too!
And there is one more goodie!
What a surprise!
How embarrassing!
Wait!
Noninjinseigami random stickers!
This is a total of 73 stickers in a box.
500 yen!
There are 3 random stickers in the package!
And what a surprise!
In syncretism
For a moment
There are some visuals that have not been released yet.
You all are welcome to guess!
Please!
So
Please join us and the Equalog Mortress Club
Let's make it matching!
For more information, please visit the official website!
Bye bye!